

# <u>(</u> + 420 601 510 102

- michalvesely4321@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/michal-vesely
- Padelky 32 Rohatec

### **EDUCATION**

High School Of Chemistry

Analysis of food

2008 - 2012

Kaplan International English

2017 - 2018

**Business And Management** 

2019 - 2021

### **SKILLS**

**HTML** 

CSS

JavaScript

WordPress

ECDL

Problem-solving

Communication

Teamwork

### LANGUAGE

English Native Czech

# MICHAL VESELY

Front-End Developer

### **About me**

My name is Michal and I have been learning coding skills by myself. I do enjoy programming in VS Code, especially HTML|CSS and JavaScript. In 2021, I made a big choice and decided to change my career path to become a web developer. I realized that this is something I would love to do, so I am passionate and interested in working as a front-end web developer. Since that time, I have kept improving my coding skills every day and I have motivation to learn new things and make use of my experience. Also, I created my own portfolio, and I am working on some projects. This is a great opportunity to change my life and do something I really love.

## **Experience**

2021 - 2023

Studying at home: Web Development

### Front-End Web Development

I created my own portfolio "https://michalkuma.github.io/frontent.github.io/" I built a function calculator by using HTML|CSS & JavaScript Keep developing skills: MySQL, PHP, Python

2017 - 2023

Uber Eats: Western Australia part time job (student)

### Delivery Driver, Customer service

Food delivery Perth City in Western Australia Customer service

2017 - 2019

IZOS: Production of insulated glass

### Officework (MS Office)

Organizing international orders and distribution Using computer software (Microsoft Office)

2013

Kindergarden Rohatec: Czech Republic part time

#### Officework (MS Office)

Parenting support, events planning Using computer software to work with data